Police people are accusing Thomas Rousseau and the Patriot Front being a federal operation, a bunch of feds.
That's because they are fucking feds and you're a fed too.
Their digital marketing used to be based off Tel Aviv before we could detect it.
The files indicate that the whole concept of the org was hashed out of Lil St. James over cocktails.
Police always cover their retreat because they get a phone call from higher ups.
Top leadership consists of former elite security who actually protected the trafficking rings that were able to transfer kids onto the island.
Of course, all the other places that they trafficked kids to, their bunkers, their castles, all their little secret facilities.
These fuck sticks played security for those operations.
Their top members are currently guarding Zorro Ranch right now as we speak.
Obviously, many of them are ICE officers and are part of a special group and department in ICE to help incorporate IOF soldiers on U.S. soil.
Yeah, anyways, in more important news, go to the screening of Seeds for Liberation in L.A. next Saturday.
Good friend Matthew Solomon put together a great documentary about the Free Palestine Movement the past three years.
As we all know, Palestine is being crushed day by day.
Genocide is ongoing and this does not stop until the state of Israel is completely obliterated.
It's something that I'm willing to say, but these fuck sticks are still not willing to say.
Go see Seeds for Liberation in L.A.
I will be there.
Hopefully, it will be a great gathering of networking for all of us in this movement who have, you know, been through it mentally, but we're still staying strong.
And we're not going to give up until Palestine is free.
As always, love you, fam.
We're not going to give up until Palestine is free.